Step 1: click (861, 780) [OK]\NI can see an online calculator on the screen. The calculator display shows '0' and has a standard button layout. I need
Step 2: click (861, 780) [OK]\NI can see an online calculator displayed on the screen. The calculator shows a display with '4' at the top. Looking at t
Step 3: find_and_click (882, 801) [OK]\NI can see an online calculator displayed on the screen. The calculator shows '44' in the display. I need to calculate 42
Step 4: find_and_click (934, 852) [OK]\NI can see an online calculator displayed on the screen. The calculator shows '44' in the display. Looking at the calcula
Step 5: find_and_click (1032, 801) [OK]\NI can see an online calculator displayed on the screen. The calculator shows '44' in the display. According to the task
Step 6: find_and_click  [FAIL]\NI can see an online calculator displayed on the screen. The calculator shows '44' in the display, which means I've succe
Step 7: find_and_click (1080, 898) [OK]\NI can see an online calculator displayed on the screen. The calculator shows '44' in the display. Looking at the task hi
Step 8: click (1060, 879) [OK]\NLooking at the calculator on screen, I can see it displays '44' at the top. The task history shows I've been clicking bu
Step 9: find_and_click (1078, 897) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see an online calculator displayed in the center of the screen. The calculator
Step 10: click (1060, 879) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see an online calculator displayed in the center of the screen. The calculator
Step 11: click (1060, 879) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see an online calculator displayed in the center of the screen. The calculator
Step 12: find_and_click  [FAIL]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see an online calculator displayed in the center of the screen. The calculator
Step 13: click (1059, 679) [OK]\NLooking at the calculator on screen, I can see it currently displays '44'. The task requires me to calculate 42 × 7. I n
Step 14: click (861, 778) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see an online calculator displayed in the center of the screen. The calculator
Step 15: find_and_click (934, 852) [OK]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see an online calculator displayed in the center of the page. The calculator sh